PHONLAPAT SUANGHIRAN

Back-End Developer

+66 65-678-1986 | PhonlapatS.2002@gmail.com | github.com/PhonlapatS | linkedin.com/in/phonlapatS

SUMMARY

A two-year Software Engineering student with a solid understanding of programming languages, including JavaScript, PHP, React, and Node.js. While I may not consider myself an expert, I am dedicated to continuous improvement and committed to achieving success in both my academic and professional pursuits. Additionally, I possess a diverse range of soft skills that enable effective collaboration and adaptability within various team settings.

EXPERIENCE

PHP Developer Part-time

March 2023 - June 2023

- Prepare the database for the website and make any necessary edits based on the customer's requirements
- Fix bugs and resolve any issues that arise on the customer's website
- Develop and edit the company's website to enhance performance and add functions to improve usability

PHP Developer Intern Feb 2022 - Oct 2022

- · Connect database to website and update backend
- Make sure to upgrade and modify the work in line with the latest customer requirements
- Assisted another Junior projects

SKILLS

- Technical Skills: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript, PHP, React, NextJS, Node.js, Express.js, SQL, AI, Prompt Engineering
- · Soft Skills: Problem solving, Adaptability, Growth mindset
- Tools: GitHub, Figma, Postman, SQLite, MySQL
- · Certifications: MySQL intermediate Certificate from HackerRank

PROJECTS

Project Performance Reporting

- Designed and developed a web-based system for reporting project performance using the PDCA model
- Secured 2nd runner-up, gold medal level for software innovation and embedded systems

Stock Management System

- Assisted in this project as a backend developer.
- Create a web system to manage stocks for small or medium-sized companies. Users can easily handle stocks, optimize management, and increase convenience without paper.

EDUCATION

High Vocational Certificate | Phrae Technical College

• Software Computer | GPAX 3.56

0-ft----- 0-----t--- | 0DAY 0.50

Rajamangala University of Technology Lanna | Chiang Mai, Doi Saket

2023 - Present

2023

• Bachelor of Engineer, Software Engineering | GPAX 3.50